Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Music Scores (The scores listed are holograph, either in pencil and/or in ink, with annotations. There are parts for: Conductor's music, Bass, Bassoon, Cello, Clarinet, Drums, Flute, Guitar, Harp, Horn, Oboe, Organ, Piano, Piccalo, Sax, Timpany, Triangle, Trombone, Trumpet, Tuba, Viola, Violins. E
  - SONG OF INDIA, Arranged by Allan Small, Printed score, 20 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - SWEETHEART, 19 pieces printed scores, undated (Box 74-77)
  - SUMMER TIME, Arranged by Leon Leonardi, 24 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - TAKES TWO TO TANGO, 12 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - TIME ON MY HANDS, 13 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - TIS THE MOMENT, 24 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - TOYLAND, 15 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - UN NOUVEAU PRINTEMPS, Arranged by Leon Leonardi, 44 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - UNA VOCE POCA FA, Arranged by Phil Lang, 24 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VICTOR NERBERT MELODIES, Arranged by Phil Lang, 16 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VILIA, Arranged by Phil Lang, 47 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - WHAT CAN A POOR MAIDEN DO, 20 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - WHO CARES, 13 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - THE WREN, Arranged by Allan Small, Printed score, 42 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 74-77)
  - YOU GO TO MY HEAD, 10 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - YOU'LL NEVER WALK ALONE, Printed score, 24 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - ZULU LULLABY (Iga'Mal'Bantwa''na), Arranged by Leon Leonardi, 14 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - ZIGEUNER, Printed score, 24 parts, Master score, undated (Box 74-77)
- Pamphlets:
  - THE HERITAGE. Home of General Andrew Jackson. Catalogue 1953. (Box 74-77)
  - HISTORIC CENTRAL CITY by Caroline Bancroft, undated (Box 74-77)
  - QUAINT OLD CHARLESTON, 1951 (Box 74-77)
- Periodicals:
  - Frank Leslie's Gazette Advertiser, Vol. V, part I - Vol. VI, Part 2. Cover gone. Not complete. Has been clipped., 1/1956, 8/1957 (Box 74-77)
  - Opera News, 1/1/1945; 1/22/1945; 4/2/1945; 4/16/1945; 11/26/1945; 4/22/1946; 11/18/1946; 1/26/1948; 4/5/1948; 12/20/1948 (Box 74-77)
  - Life, 1/2/1950 (Box 74-77)
- Phono Discs (16 inch, 33 1/3 RPM):
  - BROADCAST FROM CARNEGIE HALL OVER WJZ. Mimi Benzell and Felix Knight, 2 records. 1 side only on each., 12/13/1948 (Box 74-77)
  - Mimi Benzell - Holm interview. 1 side only., 08/06/1952 (Box 74-77)
  - FIRESTONE PROGRAM, 2 records, 1 side only., 07/24/1950 (Box 74-77)
  - ROBERT MONTGOMERY, 1 side only., 06/11/1952 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 06/19/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 07/03/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 07/10/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 07/17/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 07/24/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 07/31/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 08/07/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 08/14/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 08/21/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 08/28/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 09/04/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 09/11/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 09/18/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - JACK PEARL AND MIMI BENZELL, 1 and 2., 09/25/1951 (Box 74-77)
  - RERECORDED (only identification) Mimi Benzell, side 1 and 2., 02/25/1954 (Box 74-77)
  - ROMEO AND JULIET, Mimi Benzell, 1 side only., undated (Box 74-77)
  - MIMI BENZELL, UNA VOCE POCO FA, 1 side only., undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, 3 records, Chocolate Soldier, Brigadoon., undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, 2 records, Vagabond King, Sunny, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, 2 records, Roberta, Naughty Marietta, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, 3 records, Student Prince, Yankee, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, One Touch of Venus, Rose Marle, undated (Box 74-77)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA, Mimi Benzell, 4 records: Eileen; Bittersweet; HMS Pinafore; No, No, Nanette, undated (Box 74-77)
  - EYES ON THE FUTURE, Mimi Benzell, 3 records, side 1 and 2., undated (Box 74-77)
- Photographs:
  - 23, Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 74-77)
  - 23, publicity stills, Mimi Benzell with other celebrities, undated (Box 74-77)
  - 2, color picture of Mimi, Jonathan and Jennifer, 1957 (Box 74-77)
  - 34, miscellaneous, unidentified, undated (Box 74-77)
- Printed Music Scores:
  - Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life, 22 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Christmas Carols, 1, 19 page booklet, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Giannia Mia, 12 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Here Comes Santa Claus, 13 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - I Could Have Danced All Night, 29 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Il Baclo, 38 pieces, heavily annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Indian Love Call, 111 pieces, plus original holograph in ink, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Jewish Potpourri, 13 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - My Hero, 11 parts, undated (Box 74-77)
  - One Kiss, 47 pieces, heavily annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
  - One Alone, 19 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Romany Life, 99 pieces, heavily annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Wanting You, 16 pieces, heavily annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
  - When You’re Away, 24 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - White Christmas, 10 pieces, undated (Box 74-77)
  - You Are Love, 77 pieces, slightly annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Zigeuner, 61 pieces, annotated, undated (Box 74-77)
- Programs:
  - Metropolitan Opera House Season, 1945-1946 (Box 74-77)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Season, 1946-1947 (Box 74-77)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Season, 1947-1948 (Box 74-77)
  - Metropolitan Opera House Season, 1948-1949 (Box 74-77)
  - Alvin Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Biltmore Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Booth Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), March 21, 1943, July 11, 1943 (Box 74-77)
  - Ethel Barrymore Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Hudson Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Imperial Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - John Golden Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Lyceum Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Majestic Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - National Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), undated (Box 74-77)
  - St. James Theatre Playbill (Returned 02/23/1977), May 24, 1942, May 2, 1943 (Box 74-77)
  - Mana-Zucca Music Club, Mimi Benzell In War Bond Concert, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Stars on Ice, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Yours, A. Lincoln, undated (Box 74-77)
- Miscellaneous:
  - Small notebook, only written in 8 pages, 1939 (Box 74-77)
  - Certificate of appreciation from March of Dimes awarded to Mimi Benzell, 1962 (Box 74-77)
  - Newspaper clipping "10 Commandments of Show Biz" (worn), undated (Box 74-77)
  - Invitation to Affiliated Furniture Sales Coroporation Showing, Space 1413, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Marriage announcement, undated (Box 74-77)
  - Anniversary card, "After 11 years…", undated (Box 74-77)
  - Anniversary card, "39 years from today…", undated (Box 74-77)
  - Envelope of material from the New York University Psychological Services on Walter Gould tests (Returned 02/23/1977), 1957 (Box 74-77)
- Awards:
  - American Red Cross Award, Pittsburgh Chapter, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Golden Circle Award, Anti-Defamation League Appeal, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Honorary Citizens Award, New Orleans, June 1953 (Box 18)
  - Membership Certificate, International Who is Who in Music, July 1954 (Box 18)
  - North Shore Hadassah Award to Mimi Benzell for her appearance at the Forest of the Six Million Membership Garden Party, August 1954 (Box 18)
- Bulletin: THE DIAPER SERVICE INSITUTE OF AMERICA BULLETIN, Vol. 8, No. 2, 1955 (Box 18)
- Music Scores:
  - ALEXANDER'S RAGTIME BAND, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - AMOR, Arranged by A. Borguno, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - AT SUNDOWN, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - AUTUMN LEAVES, Arranged by Leon Leonardi, 1 part with printed music, undated (Box 19)
  - BY THE TIME I GET TO PHOENIX, 3 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 19)
  - DEAR HEART, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - DEAR HEARTS, 1 part with 3 pages of lyrics, 3 pages of notes, 2 pages of lighting cues, and a New York Mets Team Roster (with attachment), 1963 (Box 19)
  - DON'T FORGET, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - DON'T LOOK NOW, 2 parts, undated (Box 19)
  - EVER MINE, Arranged by Lou Halmy, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - FALLING IN LOVE AGAIN, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - FANFARE, 1 part, Master sheets, undated (Box 19)
  - FAR INTO THE NIGHT, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - FINALE-SHALOME, 17 parts, undated (Box 19)
  - THE GREAT MAGICIAN, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - GYPSY CARNIVAL, 1 part with one page of lyrics, undated (Box 19)
  - HAPPY HEART, Arranged by Hal Kanner, 12 parts, undated (Box 19)
  - HELLO YOUNG LOVERS, 15 parts, Master sheets (attachment), undated (Box 19)
  - I'LL SING YOU A THOUSAND LOVE SONGS, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - IN HIS HANDS, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - IN THE SPRING, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - JEFFERSON DAVIS TYLER'S GENERAL STORE, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - KINNERET, 2 parts, undated (Box 19)
  - LEAN OUT OF THE WINDOW, GOLDENHAIR, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - LOVER, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - LOVE SONG OPENING, Arranged by Hal Kanner and Jerry Bresler, 13 parts plus 1 part with attachment, one folder containing 4 parts and Master sheets, undated (Box 19)
  - MAIS OUI, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - MEET THE METS, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - MERRY WIDOW WALTZ, Arranged by A. Borguno, 1 part, undated (Box 19)
  - MILK AND HONEY, Arranged by Ted Saidenberg, Folder continaing 5 scores, 1 part each, undated (Box 19)
  - MIMI, Arranged by F. Norman, 63 parts, 2 loose pages, Master sheets, undated (Box 20)
  - MUSETTA'S WALTZ, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - MY BLUE HEAVEN, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - MY HEART STOOD STILL AND SMALL HOTEL, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - NICE MAN'S SONG, Arranged by Fred Norman, 16 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 20)
  - O DEAR! WHAT CAN THE MATTER BE?, Arranged by Arnold Bax, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - ONE KISS, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - ONE MORE ROCKIN', 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - THE PARTY'S OVER, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - PASS ME BY, 14 parts, Arranged by Hal Kanner, Master sheets, undated (Box 20)
  - PRIMAVERA, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - PSALM XXIII, Arranged by Harry E. Anik, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - RAIN HAS FALLEN, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - ROCKY, ROCKY ROAD, Arranged by R. DeCormer and L. Dobbs, 1 part, undated (Box 20)
  - SECURITY, 12 parts, 6 pages of lyrics, one page with address, undated (Box 20)
  - SHALOM, 15 parts, undated (Box 20)
  - SHALOM ALEYCHEM, Arranged by Bobby Kroll, 16 parts, undated (Box 21)
  - SHIR HACHEIRUT, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - SIMPLE AS THAT, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - SO I LOVE, Arranged by Hal Kanner, 21 parts, Master sheets, undated (Box 21)
  - A SONG IN THE NIGHT, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - THE TWO CHILDREN, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - VILLA, Arranged by Phil Lang, 2 parts, undated (Box 21)
  - WHAT THE WORLD NEEDS NOW!, Arranged by Hal Kanner, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - WHISTLE WHILE YOU WORK, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - WINTER, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
  - WORLD - LOVE SONGS, Arranged by Hal Kanner, 13 parts, undated (Box 21)
  - WUNDERBAR, 1 part, undated (Box 21)
- Negatives: Twelve 8x10 inch ektachrome negatives of Mimi Benzell, undated
- Newsletters:
  - CLINICAL CONGRESS NEWS, 2 copies, 11/17/1954 (Box 18)
  - THE THEATER TOPICS, 1954 (Box 18)
- Newspapers:
  - THE KANSAS CITY TIMES, Vol. 117, 10/16/1954 (Box 18)
  - THE POST-STANDARD, Vol. 125, 4 copies, 02/17/1954 (Box 18)
  - THE POST-STANDARD, Vol. 125, 4 copies, 02/18/1954 (Box 18)
- Newspaper Clippings:
  - 4 pieces, 1945 (Box 22)
  - 10 pieces, 1947 (Box 22)
  - 10 pieces, 1948 (Box 22)
  - 3 pieces, 1949 (Box 22)
  - 2 pieces, 1950 (Box 22)
  - 4 pieces, 1953 (Box 22)
  - 48 pieces, 1954 (Box 22)
  - 5 pieces, undated (Box 22)
- Photographs:
  - BENZELL PICTURE SET: 4, undated (Box 42)
  - BIRMINGHAM STARLITE THEATER: 2, 6- 3 1/2 x 4 1/2, 1- 6 x 9, 1- 7 x 8 1/2, 1- 7 x 9 1/4, undated (Box 42)
  - CARMEN (Micaela): 2, undated (Box 42)
  - CENTRAL CITY (Ariadne): 44, undated (Box 42)
  - CHICAGO THEATER: 3, 1- 4 1/2 x 6 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - COCOANUT GROVE: 13, undated (Box 42)
  - COTILLION ROOM: 15, 2- 6 1/2 X 8 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - DECCA RECORDS WITH ALFRED DRAKE: 5, undated (Box 42)
  - ED SULLIVAN "TOAST": 1- 7 X 8 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - FELIX KNIGHT: 1, 1- 5 X 7, undated (Box 42)
  - FIRESTONE PROGRAM: 1, undated (Box 42)
  - GORDON MACRAE/STAND ENGAGEMENT: 6, undated (Box 42)
  - JACK PEARL: 11- 6 1/2 x 8 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - LA BOHEME (Musetta): 4, undated (Box 42)
  - LAKE PLACID: 12, undated (Box 42)
  - LONDON/WAR ORPHAN JOHN: 1, 1- 4 1/2 x 6 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - MAGIC FLUTE (Queen of the Night): 9, undated (Box 42)
  - MARRIAGE OF FIGARO (Susanna): 2, undated (Box 42)
  - MIGNON (Philine): 9, undated (Box 42)
  - MORTON GOULD TOUR: 7, undated (Box 42)
  - MUSICAL COMEDY HOUR/THE CHOCOLATE SOLDIER: 4- 7 x 8 1/2, undated (Box 42)
  - MUSIC MART PROGRAM: 3, undated (Box 42)
  - NEW ORLEANS CONCERT: 1, undated (Box 42)
  - PALMER HOUSE: 4, undated (Box 42)
  - RIGOLETTO (Gilda): 4, undated (Box 42)
  - ROBERT MONTGOMERY/LUCKY STRIKE THEATER: 4, 10- 5 x 7, undated (Box 42)
  - ROSENCAVALIER (Sophie): 1- 7 1/4 x 8, 1- 6 x 8, undated (Box 43)
  - ROXY THEATRE: 5, undated (Box 43)
  - ST. LOUIS MUNICIPAL OPERA: 23, undated (Box 43)
  - STRAND THEATRE: 14, One card from stage crew, "Happy Return Mimi"., undated (Box 43)
  - SUNDAY MIRROR: 6, undated (Box 43)
  - THUNDERBIRD/LAS VEGAS: 4, undated (Box 43)
  - VARIOUS UNNAMED APPEARANCES: 1, undated (Box 43)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA: 3, undated (Box 43)
  - WHITEMAN GOODYEAR REVUE: 5, undated (Box 43)
  - WHITE PLAINS CONCERT/ZOA WITH MELCHOIR: 5, undated (Box 43)
- Photographs (Loose):
  - 39 - 5 x 7 black and white photographs of Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 43)
  - 3 - 7 x 9 black and white photographs of Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 43)
  - 7 - 7 x 9 black and white photos of Mimi Benzell and other celebrities, undated (Box 43)
  - 153 - 8 x 10 black and white photographs of Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 43)
  - 57 - 8 x 10 black and white photos of Mimi Benzell and other celebrities, undated (Box 43)
  - 3 - miscellaneous, undated (Box 43)
- Photographs (Mounted):
  - 1 - 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 of Mimi Benzell, color, undated (Box 43)
  - 1 - 7 1/4 x 9 1/4 of Mimi Benzell, St. Louis, color, undated (Box 43)
- Printed Music, Book Form:
  - THE ADULT PREPARATORY PIANO BOOK, John Thompson, The Willis Music Co., Cincinnati, 82 pages., undated (Box 34)
  - AIN'T IT A PRETTY NIGHT and THE TREES ON THE MOUNTAINS, Carlisle Ford, Boosey and Hawkes, Inc., 10 pages., undated (Box 34)
  - ALBUM OF JEROME KERN SONGS, T. B. Harms Company, New York, 47 pages., undated (Box 34)
  - ALL AMERICAN, lyrics: Lee Adams, music: Charles Strouse, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., N.Y.C., 40 pages, undated (Box 34)
  - AMERICA'S BICENTENNIAL SONGS FROM THE GREAT SENTIMENTAL AGE, Gregg Smith, editor, G. Schirmer, New York, 148 pages, undated (Box 34)
  - THE AMERICAN SONGBAG, Carl Sandburg, Harcourt, Brace and Company, New York, 521 pages, undated (Box 34)
  - ANOTHER THIRTY-FOUR HIT PARADE EXTRAS, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 84 pages, undated (Box 34)
  - ARIADNE AUF NAXOS, 82 pages, incomplete., undated (Box 34)
  - ARIETTES OUBLIEES, Jean Jobert, editor, 24 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - AUSGEWAHLTE ARIEN FUR SOPRAN, Joh. S. Bach, Ved Breitkopf and Hartel Musikverlag, Germany, 75 pages, 2 copies, undated (Box 35)
  - THE BELLS OF RHYMNEY, Pete Seeger, Oak Publications, New York, 120 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - BELOVED JEWISH SONGS FOR VOICE AND PIANO, Metro Music Company, New York, 60 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - BRAVO GIOVANNI, lyrics: Ronny Graham, Music: Milton Schafer, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc. New York, 36 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - CANCIONES CLASICAS, Fernando J. Obradors, Union Musical Espanolas Editores, Madrid, 26 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - CELEBRATED SONGS AND ARIAS, Selected and Arranged by Frank La Forge, Carl Fischer, Inc., New York, 21 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - CHANSONS POPULAIRES DE LA SUISSE ROMANDE ET ITALIENNE, Universal Edition A.G., Austria, 20 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - CHANUKKAH SONGSTER, A. W. Binder, Bloch Publishing Company, New York, 16 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - CHINA SINGS, Collected by Liu Liang-Mo, Carl Fischer, New York, 28 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - THE CHILDREN, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 1946, 46 pages (Box 35)
  - CHINESE MOTHER GOOSE RHYMES, Bainbridge Crist, Carl Fischer, New York, 14 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - COLE PORTER SONG ALBUMS, Harms, Inc., New York, 49 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - A COLLECTION OF SONGS, Ford and Erlebach, Boosey and Hawkes, LTD., London, 107 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - A CYCLUS OF FIFTEEN SONGS FOR SOPRANO OR TENOR WITH PIANOFORTE ACOMPANIMENT, G. Lynes, Arthur P. Schmidt, 51 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - DAS MADCHEN VON ELISONDO, Jacques Offenbach, Bote and Bock, Berlin, 88 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - DER JUNGE MOZART, Hinrichsen Edition, Ltd., London, 120 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - DON GIOVANNI, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 314 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - DOVER BEACH AND OTHER SONGS, by Joseph Kaufer, Lyric-Art, Illinois, 48 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - DUET PLAYING- VOL. II, Leo Podolsky, editor, Belvin, Inc., New York, 32 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - EIGHT SONGS FROM JEWISH FOLKLORE, Samuel Rosenbaum, editor, The Cantors Assembly of America, New York, 32 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - English AYRES, Transcribed and edited by Peter Warlock and Phillip Wilson, Oxford University Press, London, 38 pages, undated (Box 35)
  - EVERYBODY'S FAVORITE CHOPIN ALBUM, Amsco Music Publishing Co., New York, 128 pages., undated (Box 37)
  - VARIANTES ET POINTS D'ORGUE, Mathilde Marchesi, Heugel and Cie, Editerus, Paris, 87 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FAMOUS SONGS, H.E. Krehbiel, editor, The John Church Company, Pennsylvania, 222 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FIFTY SELECTED SONGS/Johannes Brahms, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 205 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FILLE DU REGIMENT, G. Donizetti, Pages 12-218, undated (Box 37)
  - FIRESIDE BOOK OF LOVE SONGS, Simon and Schuster, New York, 324 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FLAMMENDE ROSE, G. Fr. Handel, Kistner and Siegel and Co., Lippstadt, 10 pages with attachment, undated (Box 37)
  - FOLKSONG ARRANGEMENTS, Volume 1, British Isles, Benjamin Britten, Boosey and Hawkes Ltd., London, 24 pages, 2 copies, undated (Box 37)
  - FORTY SONGS/RICHARD STRAUSS, Oliver Ditsin Company, Philadelphia, 163 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FOUR OLD English SONGS, Music by Eric Coates, Boosey and Co., Ltd., London, 21 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FOURTY-FIVE ARIAS FROM OPERAS AND ORATORIOS, Handel, International Music Company, New York, 64 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FRA DIAVOLO, Auber, Boosey and Co., Ltd., London, 291 pages, undated (Box 37)
  - FRANZ SCHUBERT SONGS, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 318 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - FRANZ SCHUBERT SONGS, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 308 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - GEORGE M. COHAN SONG ALBUM, George M. Cohan Music Publishing Co., Inc., New York, 32 pages with attachment, undated (Box 36)
  - GEORGE M. COHAN SONG ALBUM, George M. Cohan Music Publishing Co., Inc., New York, 40 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - GREAT THEMES FROM GREAT MOVIES, Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, New York, 60 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - HEAD-OVER-HEELS, words by Sylvia Golden, music by Arthur Sullivan, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 27 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - H.M.S. PINAFORE, book by W.S. Gilbert, music by Arthur Sullivan, G. Schirmer, New York, 173 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - THE HOLY CITY, An Oratorio by A.R. Gaul, G. Schirmer, New York, 109 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - HOT SPOT, lyrics by Martin Charnin, music by Mary Rodgers, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 32 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - HOUSE OF FLOWERS, lyrics by Truman Capote and Harold Arlen, music by Harols Arlen, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 36 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - I HATE MUSIC!, Leonard Bernstein, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 16 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - IOLANTHE, written by W.S. Gilbert, composed by Arthur Sullivan, Hitchcock Publishing Company, New York, 155 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - IRISH COUNTRY SONGS, edited and arranged by Herbert Hughes, Boosey and Hawkes, New York, 85 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - ISORI-ALBUM/ALT-ITALIENISCHE ARIEN, Universal Edition, Wien, 45 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - JEWISH SONGS/FOLK AND MODERN, compiled by Henry Lefkowitch, Metro Music, New York, 112 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - JEWISH THEATRE SONGS, arranged and compiled by Jack Kammen, J. and J. Kammen Music Co., New York, 72 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - JOAQUIN NIN, Editions Max Eschig, Paris, 25 pages, undated (Box 36)
  - JOHANNES BRAHMS SONGS, Vol. 1, Edwin F. Kalmus, New York, 151 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - J.S. BACH SONGS AND AIRS, Augener Ltd., London, 74 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - LIEDER UND GESANGE, Franz Schubert, R.U.W. Lienau, Berlin, 16 pages with attachments, undated (Box 38)
  - LITTLE ME, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, music by Cy Coleman, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 44 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - LONG, LONG AGO, by Miguel Sandoval, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 14 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - MARCHESI VOCAL METHOS, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 118 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - MARTHA, music by F. von Flotow, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 213 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - MEMORIES OF JOHANN STRAUSS VOCAL ALBUM, Edward B. Marks Music Corportation, N.Y., 48 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - THE MERRY WIDOW, lyrics by Adrian Ross, music by Franz Lehar, Chappell and Co., Ltd., London, 212 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - MESSIAH, G. F. Handel, Novello and Co., Ltd., New York, 214 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - THE MIKADO, book by W.S. Gilbert, music by Arthur Sullivan, G. Schirmer, New York, 236 pages, 2 pages, undated (Box 38)
  - MORE SONGS OF THE HILL-FOLK, collected and arranged by John Jacob Niles, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 21 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - MOZART ALBUM DER MARIA STADER, Universal Edition, Wein, 85 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - MOZART/THIRTY SONGS, Augener Ltd., London, 80 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - NEW MUSIC FOR THE PIANO, selected by Joseph Prostakoff, Lawson-Gould Music Publishers, Inc., New York, 107 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - OLD AMERICAN SONGS, Aaron Copland, Boosey and Hawkes, New York, 24 pages, 2 copies, undated (Box 40)
  - OLD English MELODIES, words and music arranged by B. Lane Wilson, Boosey and Hawkes, Inc., New York, 95 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - OPERATIC ANTHOLOGY, edited by Max Spicker, G. Schirmer, New York, 289 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - PETER PAN, lyrics by Carolyn Leigh, music by Mark Charlap, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 28 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - PIANO LITERATURE OF THE 17TH, 18TH, AND 19TH CENTURIES, edited by Louise Goss, Summy-Birchard Publishing Company, 47 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - THE PIRATES OF PENZANCE, written by W. S. Gilbert, composed by Arthur Sullivan, J.M. Stoddart and Co., 139 pages, undated (Box 40)
  - THE PRIMA DONNA'S ALBUM, edited by Josiah Pittman, G. Schirmer, New York, 331 pages, undated (Box 40)